#### D C SUDHAN

BIRTHDAY: 7th June 1996 (26 years)

EMAIL: sudhandc7@gmail.com

## SKILL SUMMARY

Full Stack Engineer with 4 years of working experience with startups. Experience in System design, development, delivery, and maintenance of complex applications using a variety of programming languages and technologies. Expert in Ruby On rails, Go, JavaScript (VueJs), PHP and MySql.

# TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Key Areas: Backend, Docker, Rest Api, Third Party Api Integration, AWS, CI/CD
- Language: Ruby, JavaScript (Vue.js), Golang, PHP, Java, Android
- Framework: Rails, Gin (Go), Codeigniter
- Methodologies: Agile and Waterfall
- VCS: Git, Bitbucket

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Cloco.Inc.

Full Stack Engineer (Feb 2019 – Present)
Ochanomizu, Tokyo (<a href="https://www.cloco.co.jp/">https://www.cloco.co.jp/</a>)

### Responsibilities:

- dockerize image to manage the golang application and build RESTful Apies.
- Create AWS server using terraform and deploy the project.
- Engaged to plan, develop web app and repair site issues and queries.
- Lead development in a bike sharing service and restaurant reservation system in Tokyo, using Ruby on Rails as the backend and Vue.js as frontend.
- Implemented architectural design for backend application structures and databases.
- Understand the project requirements clearly and create work flow diagrams and Gant chart diagram to clearly demonstrate processes and timelines.
- Write test code (RSpec)/(Go) and refactor code to improve code quality.

## **Emultitech Solution Pvt.Ltd**

Junior Developer (Feb 2017 – June 2018)

Kupondole, Lalitpur, Nepal (https://www.emultitechsolution.com/)

## Responsibilities:

- Worked as a highly resourceful, innovative, and competent PHP developer with extensive
- experience in developing of websites specifically in PHP CI framework.
- Understand the project requirements clearly and verify the product with SRS.
- Generate queries in case there is any confusion in understanding the project.
- Building Api for mobile app development and Integrate third party Api such as PayPal, AWS SNS, Facebook, Instagram.

# **EDUCATION**

- Bachelor: Tribhuvan University (T.U) Oct 2013 Nov 2017, Bachelor's in information Management (BIM), Passed with Distinction (3.57 GPA)
- 10+2: Higher Secondary Education Board, July 2011– July 2013, Passed with first Division.
- S.L.C: Nepal Government Jun 2011 S.L.C Passed with first Division

# SPEAKING LANGUAGE

Nepali: Native English: Fluent

Japanese: Business Proficiency (Difficult to read kanji)

**Hindi:** Business Proficiency

### **OTHERS:**

Coding, Playing Football, Dancing, Travelling.